{"allRoundData":[
  {
    "name": "Level 1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "timeLimitInSeconds": 20,
    "pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer": 1,
    "questions": [
      {
        "questionText": "What do frogs eat?",
        "ansChoice": [ "Honey Stars", "Flies", "Porkchops", "Chicken Rice" ],
        "correctAns": 2
      },
      {
        "questionText": "Where do mice live?",
        "ansChoice": [ "In the sea", "On the moon", "On land", "In a tree" ],
        "correctAns": 3
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "Level 2",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "timeLimitInSeconds": 20,
    "pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer": 1,
    "questions": [
      {
        "questionText": "What do frogs eat?",
        "ansChoice": [ "Honey Stars", "Flies", "Porkchops", "Chicken Rice" ],
        "correctAns": 2
      },
      {
        "questionText": "Where do mice live?",
        "ansChoice": [ "In the sea", "On the moon", "On land", "In a tree" ],
        "correctAns": 3
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "Level 3",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "timeLimitInSeconds": 20,
    "pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer": 1,
    "questions": [
      {
        "questionText": "What do frogs eat?",
        "ansChoice": [ "Honey Stars", "Flies", "Porkchops", "Chicken Rice" ],
        "correctAns": 2
      },
      {
        "questionText": "Where do mice live?",
        "ansChoice": [ "In the sea", "On the moon", "On land", "In a tree" ],
        "correctAns": 3
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "Level 4",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "timeLimitInSeconds": 20,
    "pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer": 1,
    "questions": [
      {
        "questionText": "What do frogs eat?",
        "ansChoice": [ "Honey Stars", "Flies", "Porkchops", "Chicken Rice" ],
        "correctAns": 2
      },
      {
        "questionText": "Where do mice live?",
        "ansChoice": [ "In the sea", "On the moon", "On land", "In a tree" ],
        "correctAns": 3
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "Level 5",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "timeLimitInSeconds": 20,
    "pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer": 1,
    "questions": [
      {
        "questionText": "What do frogs eat?",
        "ansChoice": [ "Honey Stars", "Flies", "Porkchops", "Chicken Rice" ],
        "correctAns": 2
      },
      {
        "questionText": "Where do mice live?",
        "ansChoice": [ "In the sea", "On the moon", "On land", "In a tree" ],
        "correctAns": 3
      }
    ]
  }
 ]}